我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标 活下去
For five years,I was stranded on an
island,with only one goal: Survive.
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish...
根据他留给我的名单
to use the list of names he left me,
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
and bring down those who
are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
所以你见到帽衫男了
Previously on "Arrow"...
他之前联系过我
So you met up with the Hood guy? He's contacted me before.
你这个杀人凶手
You're a murderer.
你曾是我这辈子最好的朋友
可现在我完全不懂你了
You were my best friend in life,but
now it's like I don't even know you.
我不干了
I quit.
听着 Lyla Lawton是个危险人物
Listen,Lyla,Lawton is
a very dangerous man.
你了解他吗
What do you know about him?
这些足以帮你查出谁指使死亡射手了
That's everything you need to locate
who's giving Deadshot his targets.
这个Lawton踢了他的狗还是怎么了
This Lawton kick his dog or something?
他杀了他哥哥
He killed his brother.
知道他逍遥法外 我就不得安宁
I can't move on with my life
knowing that he's still out there.
我以为你能懂我
I thought if anybody
got that it'd be you.
你们还有恩怨未了
You two have unfinished business.
从哪里下手
Where do we start?
感觉好点了吗
You feel better?
干掉死亡射手我就能好了
I'll feel better once we end Deadshot.
欢迎来德国 大使先生
Welcome to Germany,Mr. Ambassador.
Henrik 气色不错呀
Henrik,you're looking great.
在更多女人丧夫前 我们得干掉他
We have to end this guy before he
makes any more widows out of wives.
我们当然要
We will.
Diggle 我们会阻止他的
Diggle,we'll stop him.
我答应过你打倒他 我决不食言
I promised you I'd help take
him down,and I keep my promises,
可他在另一块大陆上
but he's on another continent.
现在回来了
Not anymore.
我觉得追踪超人类研究组
I thought it would be helpful
to track A.R.G.U.S' manhunt
有助于追捕死亡射手Floyd Lawton
所以我破译了他们的通讯记录
for Floyd Lawton aka Deadshot,so I
decrypted their communication logs.
就是说 我入侵了一个联邦机构
Which means,I just Which kind of makes
hacked a federal agency.
弄得我有点像网络恐怖分子了
me a cyber-terrorist,
糟糕 我可不适合关塔那摩湾监狱
which is bad because I really don't see
myself fitting in well at Guantanamo Bay.
别担心 Felicity
他们不会把金发美女关进去的
Don't worry,Felicity,they
don't send blondes there.
我这发色其实是染的
I dye it,actually.
我保守了你的秘密...
I keep your secret...
嘿 有什么发现
Hey,what'd you find?
死亡射手会在斯特林市和一潜在客户见面
Deadshot is scheduled to meet with a
potential new client here in Starling City.
可这次交易是假的
Except the potential contract is bogus.
你朋友Lyla设了陷 Lawton上钩了
太好了 我去跟Lyla谈
看看能不能套出细节
Your friend Lyla is setting a
trap for him. Lawton took the bait.
好 我得去和Laurel吃午饭了
Great,I'll talk to Lyla,see Good. I've got to
if I can suss out any details. have lunch with Laurel.
你何时成了她的御用午餐伴
So when did you become,uh,lunch
dates with Laurel?
我们只是...只是朋友
Look,we're just... We're friends.
- 是朋友很好啊
- 但是
- Friends are good.
- But?
你结交朋友能别那么复杂吗
她是你的前女友呢
Couldn't you be friends with someone
less complicated than your ex-girlfriend,
还是你前好友的现任女友
who's your ex-best
friend's current girlfriend?
我穿帽衫杀罪犯
I wear a hood and I put
arrows into criminals,
即使情况复杂 我也能顺利过关
so when it comes to
complexity... I grade on a curve.
营救你爸爸 阻止Fyers
并不像公园散步那么简单
Rescuing your father and stopping Fyers
is not going to be some walk in the park.
他们不会让我们在军营里晃荡的
They're not going to allow us to
just stroll on into their camp.
所以我们需要掩护
Which is why we'll need cover.
若我俩都要进敌营 谁来掩护
If both of us are
infiltrating,who'll provide that?
他来
He will.
我吗
Me?
那冲锋枪进水了
The assault rifle is flushed.
没用了
It's useless.
我们有弓箭
We have a bow,arrows.
可没人会用
And no one capable of shooting them.
无意冒犯啊 小鬼
No offense,kid.
你抢了我的台词
I was going to say the same thing.
我觉得大家应该多花点时间制定计划
I think we should be spending
our time trying to devise a plan,
而不是缩小那本就一线的生机
not lower our already
slim chances of survival.
他会在日落前学会射箭
He'll hit his mark by sundown.
如果学不会 就听你的
If not,we'll do it your way.
Lyla
Lyla!
什么事 Johnnie
What is it,Johnnie?
就来看看对死亡射手的调查
Just came by to see how things were
going on your Deadshot investigation.
有什么进展吗
Anything new come up?
还真有
Funnily enough,it did.
我本来很好奇 你一个保镖
I was curious why you,a bodyguard,
为何如此执着于抓捕臭名昭著的杀手
were so keen on taking down
such a high profile assassin,
所以我调查了Lawton
so I did some reading up on Lawton.
Lyla 听我说...
Lyla,listen...
你以为我查不出他是你杀兄仇人吗
Did you really think I wouldn't
find out that he killed your brother?
你一直在利用我
That you were using me...me!
为什么 引他出来 手刃仇敌吗
To what? Draw him into the open so
you could take him down yourself?
我不会让你利用我的人来报仇雪恨的
I will not let you use my
agency to settle your blood feud.
Lyla 这人必须死
Lyla... I need to see this guy in a bag.
你应该懂我
You of all people should get that.
听清楚 离Lawton远点 Johnnie
再插手 就别怪我抓你了
Get this...stay away from Lawton,Johnnie,or
so help me,I will have you arrested.
不信我说到做到吗
You doubt me?
我不敢
Never have.
收到我的语音信息了吗
Did you get my voicemail?
没
No.
情况有点失控了 连着开了好几个会
Things got a little crazy around
here... back to back meetings...
真是抱歉 下次再一起吃饭吧
I am so sorry,rain check?
没事
Sure.
我正好夜店那边有好多文件要看
I could definitely catch
up on some club paperwork.
Tommy一走 很多事就拖着了
We're way behind since Tommy left.
我还是很惊讶 他居然去帮Malcolm了
I'm still shocked that he
went to go work for Malcolm.
你肯让他去 真是太善解人意了
You know,you were really understanding
to let him take this opportunity.
Tommy说你同意了
Tommy said you were cool with it.
何乐不为呢 他跟你一样 是我朋友
Why wouldn't I be? He's
my friend. Like you.
对不起  我们来早了吗
I'm sorry,are we early?
没 没有
No,not at all.
Oliver 这是Eric Moore 他妻子Nancy
Uh,Oliver,this is Eric
Moore and his wife,Nancy.
我要帮他们准备明天的口供
I'm prepping them for a
deposition for tomorrow.
这应该就是你们的保镖吧
And this must be your bodyguard?
他是我们儿子 Taylor
This is our son,Taylor.
她是很棒的律师
Well,you are in very capable hands.
很高兴见到你们
It was nice to meet you.
Eric Nancy 你们确定准备好了吗
Eric,Nancy,I want to make sure
that you guys are up for this.
Edward Rasmus不好对付
Edward Rasmus isn't known
for playing with kid gloves,
前路困难重重啊
so this could get rough.
我们的毕生积蓄都投资给Rasmus
他却欺骗我们
We invested our entire life
savings with Rasmus and he stole it.
包括我们的退休金
Our retirement.
Taylor上大学的钱
Taylor's college fund.
他偷了我们的未来 Lance小姐
He stole our future,Ms. Lance.
我们想要回来
We want it back.
那好 就去要回来吧
Well,then let's go get it.
谁啊
Hello?
Moore先生 Lance小姐有些文件给你
Mr. Moore? I have some documents for you
是关于明天的口供
from Ms. Lance related
to tomorrow's deposition.
你家真漂亮
What a nice home you have here.
在这你可以真切地感受到爱
You can really... Feel the love.
弄这么乱 真抱歉
Sorry about the mess.
弄得像入室抢劫 会好一点
This works better if it
looks like a break-in.
- 搞定了吗
- 那对夫妻搞定了
- Is it done?
- The parents,yes.
但恐怕有变数 那小孩跑了
I'm afraid there's been a
variable. The child got away.
跑了
Got away?
他看见你了吗
Did he see you?
没 Rasmus先生
No,Mr. Rasmus.
他要看见谁 那就是送他上西天了
What he saw was the face of the man
who will reunite him with his parents.
斯特林市将举办今年的灯展
Starling City is expected to be host of
this year's Festival of Lights exhibition.
另一则消息 Moore夫妇的尸体
在今早被发现
In other news,the bodies of Mr. and
Mrs. Moore were found early this morning.
法律援助所的Laurel Lance代表这对夫妇
The couple were being represented
by attorney Laurel Lance of CNRI
起诉金融家Edward Rasmus
in a lawsuit against
financier Edward Rasmus.
他们七岁的儿子Taylor
奇迹般地逃过此劫
Miraculously,their seven-year-old son
Taylor survived the horrific attack.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 骗骗米 Ducky Rosemary 胖梨
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴: 与雅安同在
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:与雅安同在
绿箭侠
第一季 第二十集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 20
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
这不是你的错 Laurel
你不该为此自责
This isn't your fault,Laurel,you
shouldn't feel guilty.
我没自责 我是生气
I don't feel guilty. I'm angry.
这不是随便的入室抢劫
This wasn't some random break-in.
Edward Rasmus有参与 我知道
Edward Rasmus is involved,I know it.
听着 我们的人在调查此事
Ok,listen,our guys
are looking into this.
你不要涉入此事 好吗
But you need to stay out of it,ok?
因为如果Rasmus是幕后推手
他可不是闹着玩玩
Because if Rasmus is behind
this,he's clearly not messing around.
你们要不要和Taylor道别一下
Uh... If you'd like to
say good-bye to Taylor,
我要带他去托管所了
I will be taking him
over to child services.
他没别的家人吗
Doesn't he have any other family?
祖父母在墨尔本
Grandparents are in Melbourne.
我在联系他们 联系上之前
We're tracking them down,but until then,
他就先在美国待着
he's going to be a
temporary ward of the state.
我可以带着他
He can stay with me.
作为他的律师
我任命自己为临时监护人
As his attorney,I am assigning
myself temporary guardianship.
你还是需要法院指令
You'd still need a judge's order.
一小时后给你
I'll have it to you in an hour.
随你吧
Well,have it your way.
我去把巡逻车停在你家外
Ok,look,I'm going to park a
patrol car outside your place.
好
Fine.
你照顾他们 行吗
And you... You look
after them,all right?
反正我常在你女儿家过夜
I spend most nights at
your daughter's anyways.
可能现在说这个不合适
There was probably a better
time to tell you that.
可能是
Probably not.
你要来住我家啦 好吗
Hey,come stay in my house,ok?
- 你在这干嘛
- 我听说发生的事了
- What are you doing here?
- I heard what happened.
我想确保Laurel没事
I just wanted to make
sure Laurel was ok.
打电话来就好
You could have just called.
我昨天见到Laurel的客户
和他们儿子了 我很难过
I met Laurel's clients and their
son yesterday and I felt badly.
你见到他们了
You met them?
我接Laurel去吃午餐时
Yeah,when I was picking
up Laurel for lunch...
她没跟你说
Which she didn't tell you about.
说什么
Tell you what?
没事
Nothing.
安顿好了
It's settled.
Taylor今晚和我们回家
Taylor's coming home with us tonight.
- 要是你需要什么...
- 我们很好
- Well,if you need anything...
- we're fine.
好吧
Ok.
我们真该走了
We should really get going.
走吧
Here.
瞄准
Set your sight.
射树
Hit the tree.
没射准那棵树
Probably hit a tree.
瞄准
Set your sight.
射树
Hit the tree.
稳住瞄准点
Steady your anchor point.
我希望你们走得
离教他成为神射手更近了
I hope you're getting closer... At
teaching him how to be a better marksman.
倒不是我们就指着这活呢
It's not as though our lives
depend on it or anything.
- 再试次
- 好
- Try again.
- Ok.
这是什么
What's this?
Lyla为死亡射手设埋伏的任务档案
Lyla's mission profile on the
trap they've set for Deadshot.
Lawton被安排见他的新雇员
明晚八点拿到任务
Lawton is set to meet his new employer
and get his assignment tomorrow at 8 pm.
只是 他的新雇员...会是探员
Only,his new employer...
Will be an A.R.G.U.S. agent.
Lyla会带队趁虚而入 逮捕他
Lyla will then swoop in
with her team and arrest him.
你想让Lawton被捕吗
Do you want Lawton arrested?
不想
No.
那明晚 我们
把Floyd Lawton的名从名单上划掉
Then tomorrow night,we cross
Floyd Lawton's name off your list.
还有些东西要查下
There is something else
we need to look into.
两位Laurel的客户昨晚被害
Two of Laurel's clients
were murdered last night.
他们7岁的儿子死里逃生
Their seven-year-old
son barely escaped.
真是糟
That's terrible.
Edward Rasmus
那个Laurel带上法庭的理财顾问
Edward Rasmus,the financial
advisor Laurel was taking to court,
可能没开枪 但他可能计划了抢劫
may not have pulled the trigger,but
he probably called in the hit.
我想让你调查他的公司账户
通话记录
I want you to get into his
corporate accounts,phone records,
所以与犯罪有关的
anything that may link
him to the killer,ok?
你去哪
Where are you going?
Laurel家
Laurel's.
又是朋友聚会吗
Another friendly meal?
- 我女儿在她住处还安全吗
- 目前来说是 没有异常
- My daughter is secure at her place?
- So far,all quiet...
要是有动作就告诉我
All right,let me know
if there is any movement.
我现在就过去
I'm heading over there right now.
你这次偷了什么
What did you steal this time?
- 你有时间吗
- 没
- You got a minute?
- No.
是有关帽衫侠的事
It's about the Hood.
你被绑架后 我的人地铁上发现你时
When my men found you on that
subway car after you were kidnapped,
你说你不知道义务警员的事
you told them you didn't know
anything about the vigilante.
你有什么忘说了吗
So there's something
you forgot to tell them?
没有
No.
我只是像大家一样想看他被绳之于法
I just want to see him brought
to justice like everyone else.
别担心 孩子 我们会抓住他的
Don't worry,kid. We'll get him.
可别给个理由让我抓你
Just keep making sure I don't
have a reason to get you.
Taylor 亲爱的
Taylor? Sweetheart?
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
我做奶酪通心粉一绝哦
You know,I make the world's
best macaroni and cheese.
她只会做这个
It's the only thing
she knows how to make.
我想爸爸妈妈
I miss my mom and dad.
我像你这个年龄时
我妈在出门前给我掖好被子
When I was your age,my mom tucked me
into bed that night before going out.
接下来就是警察来了
Then the next thing I knew,there
was a police officer at my door.
他说她走了 我再也见不到她了
但你知道吗
He said that she was gone and that I would
never see her again. But you know what?
他错了
He was wrong.
你见到她了
You saw her?
我每闭上眼 就能见到她
Every time I close
my eyes,I can see her.
每晚入睡 都在梦乡中见到她
Every time I go to bed,I
see her in my dreams.
真的吗
Really?
嗯
Yeah.
试试 闭上眼
Now try it,close your eyes.
我看到他们了
I see them.
你伤心或难过的时候
记住他们都会在你身边
Whenever you are sad,or scared,just
remember that they will always be there.
你总是给我惊喜 Merlyn
You constantly surprise me,Merlyn.
我去开
I'll get it.
Lance小姐
Ms. Lance?
Kessel上尉 斯特林城警察
Lieutenant Kessel,SCPD.
你爸让我来看看
Your dad asked me to check in.
上尉 你能出示你的警徽吗
Lieutenant,can you hold your
badge up to the door,please?
好
Ok,great.
等一下
Just one sec.
什么
What?
他警徽上的工号是0开头
上尉的工号是1开头...
His badge number begins with a zero,Lieutenant's
badge numbers begin with a one...
是警徽穿帮了 对吧
It was the badge that
gave me away,right?
我爸是警察
You know,my father's a cop.
他可不光教了我这些
And that's not all he taught me.
你该搬家了
I'm feeling like it might
be time for you to move.
爸 Rasmus雇的人不杀我不会罢休
Dad,whoever Rasmus hired is going to
keep coming until he finishes the job,
不然Rasmus也会再雇人来杀我
otherwise Rasmus will just
hire someone else who will.
听着 我想对你们仨
立即实行保护性监禁
Ok,listen,I want the three of you
in protective custody immediately,
别犹豫了
and don't even think about it.
他杀了我两个手下
He killed two of my men.
帽衫侠刚刚救了我们
The Hood just saved our lives.
我们能相信他
We can trust him.
他不会让我出事的
He won't let anything happen to me.
即使我想让他全天候保护你
Even if I was comfortable with the
idea of him watching over you 24/7,
当然我不想 我觉得他有更重要的事要做
which I'm not,something tells
me he's got better things to do.
那Oliver呢
What about Oliver?
你还有别的朋友叫Oliver吗
Sorry,you got another
friend named Oliver?
Queen一家比总统安保措施还多
The Queens have more
security than the President.
哪里都有监控 各处都有保镖
They've got cameras
everywhere,bodyguards in every wing,
进出需要理由
and no one goes in or out
without being accounted for.
我们都知道什么对Laurel最好
We both only want what
is best for Laurel.
眼下是在Oliver身边
And right now that is
to stay close to Oliver.
相信我
Trust me.
这是Robbins先生
This is Mr. Robbins.
你去哪 他去哪
Where you go,he goes.
我会保护好你的 Lance小姐
You'll be very well protected,Ms. Lance.
谢谢
Thank you.
我亲自挑选了这些保镖
I hand-selected these men myself.
房子和院子都很安全
The house and the grounds
are completely secure.
当自己家 不用拘束
Please make yourself at home.
你就是Taylor吧
You must be Taylor.
我告诉你好吃的曲奇藏哪了 好不好呀
How about I show you where
I hide the good cookies?
Queen先生 等你准备好了
Mr. Queen,whenever you're ready,
我带你去下一个地方
I can take you to your
next appointment,sir.
去见Lawton吗
The Lawton meeting?
是的
Yes.
我得先去趟俱乐部 拿一下我的外套
I just need to swing by the
club and pick up my good suit.
你在那里等我吧
So,I'll meet you there.
好的
Of course,sir.
你要出门吗
You're leaving?
我还有其他事要处理 很重要
There's something else I need
to take care of. It's important.
比这儿的事还重要吗
More important than
what's going on here?
无意冒犯
No offense to Oliver,
但我认为比起Oliver
我们更需要Robbins先生和他的手下
but I think we need Mr. Robbins
and his men more than him.
你是我们来这的原因
相信我 我很不乐意承认这一点
You are the reason why we're here,and
trust me,that wasn't easy to admit.
你们会没事的
You'll be fine.
我保证
I promise.
你知道吗 嚼东西会缓解压力
You know,chewing might help.
你觉得不好吃吗
Not dainty enough for you?
不要忘了
I could eat you under
the table,Roy Harper.
我可以偷偷把你吃了 Roy Harper
Don't forget that.
所有小组注意 发生爆炸
斯特林市港口发生爆炸
什么声音
All units,code 10-80.
Starling City port,10-80...
怀疑义务警员所为 请求支援
What is that? Suspected vigilante
activity,requesting all available units.
你口袋里有警方的对讲机吗
Do you have a police
radio in your pocket?
没有 很高兴见到你
No,I'm just happy to see you.
我得走了
Got to run.
我想你拿了我的东西
I think you've got
something that belongs to me.
你设下这个局 只是为了拿回对讲机吗
You set this up,just
to get your radio back?
对 我很喜欢那个对讲机
Well... I do love that radio.
快点
Come on.
我把广场的卫星俯视图发到你手机上了
I'm uploading a satellite overview
of the Plaza to your phone...
多谢 但是我很熟悉那个地方
Thanks,but I know the place...
Dig对你该藏的位置很上心
Dig was pretty specific about
where you should perch...
你知道的 那样能给Lawton致命一击
you know,what position gives
you the best shot at Lawton.
我这样认为
I think.
他说了很多军事术语
He used a lot of military jargon.
你要反狙击
So you're sniping a sniper.
听上去有点讽刺 是吧
Kind of ironic,don't you think?
我没有
Me neither.
这是什么
What's that?
我用远程木马在网上查找Edward Rasmus
I had a remote access trojan scouring
the Internet for Edward Rasmus.
他的名字突然出现在航空公司名单上
8：15的飞机去上海
His name just popped up on a
flight manifest,8:15 to Shanghai...
- 他想逃跑
- 很好 不是吗
- He's running.
- That's good,right?
如果他跑了
就不会再追杀Laurel和那孩子
If he's leaving town,he won't be
after Laurel and the child anymore.
不过你要是想阻止他 现在是最好的机会
But if you did want to stop
him,looks like it's now or never.
死亡射手还是Rasmus... 你自己选
Deadshot or Rasmus... Your choice.
诱捕1队 这里是先头人员
Trap one,this is Harbinger.
等Lawton进去接头
Wait for Lawton to
enter and make contact.
我们把他拿下
Then we'll take him down.
该死 Oliver
Damn it,Oliver...
等法律援助协会的风波平息后
Just until this CNRI mess dies down.
如果没有搞定 去中国的好处是
吃馄饨而且不用引渡条款
And if it doesn't,two best things about
China... wontons and no extradition treaty.
嘿 我想我有花钱让你不要停红灯
Hey,hey,I thought I was paying
you extra not to stop at the reds.
诱捕1队 可疑目标出现
Trap one,possible target acquisition.
准备好
Get ready.
退下
Stand down.
可能Lawton没有上钩
Maybe Lawton didn't
take the bait after all.
我们已经暴露 快掩护
We're blown! Take cover!
跪下 跪下
On your knees. On your knees.
把手放在头后面
Hands behind your head.
隔1英里远我就看到你过来了
I saw you coming a mile away.
多谢替我转移视线
Thanks for tipping me off.
我要杀了你 为Andy报仇
I'll kill you for what you did to Andy.
要不是因为没人付钱 我现在就杀了你
I'd be pulling these triggers right
now,except there's nobody paying me.
这儿给你留着位置 就在你哥哥旁边
There's space for you right
here,right next to your brother.
你最好记住了
You'd do best to remember that.
发生什么了
What happened?
你没有出现 事情进展不是很顺利
You didn't show,things didn't go well.
Rasmus要逃跑 我得权衡重要性
Rasmus was skipping town...
And I had to reprioritize.
因为你的权衡 4名警员死了 Oliver
Thanks to your new priorities
four agents are dead,Oliver.
你本可以阻止他 杀了这个疯子
You could have stopped this guy,ended
this maniac once and for all.
Lawton逃了吗
Lawton got away?
你真的认为被称为"死亡射手"的人
会乖乖束手就擒吗
You seriously think a man who goes by the
name "Deadshot" was going down without a fight?
我当时需要你 伙计
I needed you there,man.
Taylor Moore需要我 Diggle
Taylor Moore was relying on me,Diggle.
这跟那个孩子无关
他在戒备森严的房子里很安全
But this was never about that kid,he is
safe under armed security at your house.
这是为了Laurel
This is about Laurel.
Diggle 我必须做个选择
Diggle,I made a choice.
我知道
I know.
你选了Laurel
You chose Laurel.
总是她
Always her.
其他人都该死
Everybody else be damned.
有什么想说的 Felicity
Something to say,Felicity?
你不想听的
Nothing you want to hear.
再试试
Try again.
你想得太多了
You're thinking too much.
从没有人这么说过我
Nobody ever accused me of that before.
炫耀
Show-off.
看见远处的目标 感受风的变化
I see my target in the distance,I
feel the variation in the wind,
感觉弦拉紧了 放手
I hear the bowstring
tighten... And I let go.
相信你的感觉 不要多想
Give in to your senses... Don't think.
你说的对 这绝对不合时宜
You're right,this is definitively
not the time or place...
不...不 只是...因为某人
No,it's...no,it's just
there's,uh... Someone.
事情很复杂 但是我不能
And it's a mile past
complicated,but I can't.
她知道你有多爱她吗
Does she know how much you love her?
我想她现在不知道
I suspect right now she doesn't.
但是一旦我回家了 她会知道的
But as soon as I'm home,she will.
那天晚上你太漂亮了
You looked so beautiful that night.
我记得Oliver告诉我过
I remember Oliver telling me
once that he wished your father
他希望你父亲能够
允许他多拜访你们家
would let him come over
to your house more often.
在那里他更能找到自我
而不是Robert Queen的儿子
That being there made him feel less like
Robert Queen's son and more like himself.
我喜欢看到在你身边的他
I liked who my son was
when he was around you.
谢谢
Thank you.
警方刚刚来电
The police just called.
Edward Rasmus已经被捕
Edward Rasmus was arrested.
真的吗 发生什么了
Really? What happened?
显然他承认了一切
Apparently he confessed to everything.
他会在狱中呆很久 再也不能伤害任何人
He's going to go to prison for a long time
and won't be able to hurt anyone ever again.
他为什么会认罪呢
Why would he confess?
义务警员帮了忙
The vigilante was involved.
很好
Good for him.
我想事情结束了
So,I guess it's over.
是
Yes...Yeah.
太好了 我去把Taylor叫醒
Great,I'll go wake up Taylor...
别 Tommy 他在睡觉
这几天他经历了太多
No,Tommy,please. He's
sleeping,he's been through a lot.
很欢迎你们都住下
Now you all are welcome to stay.
我们绝对有足够的房间
We certainly have enough room.
听你的
It's your call.
多谢 Queen夫人
Thank you,Mrs. Queen.
我想那我们就住下吧
I guess we'll stay,then.
好的
Good.
你的律师到了
Your lawyer's here.
我们得商量下怎么收场
I'd like to discuss loose ends.
你没收到我的信息吗
You didn't get my message?
不要管Moore家的孩子了
Forget about the Moore boy.
我已经认罪了 那个帽衫怪物说
我要是不认罪就杀了我
I've already confessed,that freakshow in
a hood told me he'd kill me if I didn't.
我们得让这次见面看起来像模像样
We need to make this
meeting appear legitimate.
律师该做的
Lawyer stuff.
签这里
Sign here,please.
你听清楚了吗 不要管那个孩子了
Am I clear? You leave the boy alone.
我也乐意放他一条生路
可他见过我的脸
I wish I could,but he's seen my face.
就像你一样
Just like you.
如果你按压小臂上的这块皮肤
就像这样
If you put pressure in just the
right areas above the forearm,
内侧前臂静脉中会形成塞栓
like I did to you,an embolism will
form in the medial antebrachial vein.
大概十五秒之后 当气穴到达你的心脏
When the air pocket reaches your
heart in,give or take,fifteen seconds,
你就会安然无痛地死去
you'll die. It's relatively painless.
我这么做并非是针对你
Nothing personal.
我们完事了
We're done here!
打扰一下 我在找我男朋友
他是这的常客
Excuse me,hi,I'm looking for my
boyfriend,he's kind of a regular around here.
锐利的蓝眼睛 或许偷了个警员对讲机
Piercing blue eyes,and may or may
not have stolen a police radio.
哦 他就在你身后
Yeah,that's him. Behind you.
你看起来气色不错啊
Well,that's a nice look.
- 你脑子里到底在想什么啊
- 如果这不是正在上演非凡兄弟组...
- What were you thinking?
- Well,if it isn't the wonder twins...
他很抱歉偷了对讲机
He's very sorry for stealing the radio,
他再也不会给你们找麻烦
或者从这偷东西了
and he won't ever bug you or steal
anything from you guys ever again.
你们俩 跟我过来
Both of you. Come with me.
你带我们来这干什么
What are we doing here?
既然你男友对帽衫男这么感兴趣
Well,your boyfriend is
so interested in the Hood,
我猜他会想见见帽衫男的老熟人
I thought he might like to meet someone
else who already made his acquaintance.
哦 天哪...
Oh,God...
他是谁
Who was he?
事实上 你活着的时候有名字
Well,that's the thing. When
you're alive,you get a name.
等你在这挺尸的时候 就只剩个编号了
When you wind up down
here,you get a number.
他是26号
Meet 26.
自打你那位帽衫男哥们开始独自为战
See,your pal the Hood,he's
already sent 26 stiffs down here
他已经给这添了26具尸体了
since he started his
little one-man... War.
- 或许是因为这人该死
- 或许确是如此
- Maybe this guy deserved it.
- Maybe he did.
但他不该用这种方式伸张正义
But that's not how justice works.
那位义务警员无需在意
除他自己之外的任何人
You see,the vigilante,he doesn't
have to answer to anyone but himself,
任何人若是有此等权力都是件危险的事
and that's a very dangerous
power to give to any one man.
他救了我一命
He saved my life.
你怎么知道他明天不会又随手把你干掉
And how do you know tomorrow
he won't just as easily take it?
出去吧
Get out of here.
走吧
Let's go.
他现在安全了 Laurel
He's safe now,Laurel.
但前路坎坷
With a hard road ahead of him.
他能遇到你真是太幸运了
Well,he's lucky to have you in his life.
我对这体会感同身受
I know the feeling.
你刚回来的时候 我觉得你还是老样子
When you first got home,I didn't
think that you changed much.
但你的确变了... 变得更好了
But you have,and... It's nice to see.
谢谢
Thank you.
有辆货车来送东西给Lance小姐
身份已查对无误
I have a delivery van coming in
for Ms. Lance,his I.D. checks out.
多谢提醒
Thanks for the heads up.
这是给Lance小姐的
For...Ms. Lance.
多么漂亮的家啊
What a beautiful home.
却弥漫着一股痛苦的气息
Such pain here.
地板散发出一种失意和悔恨的味道...
A sense of loss and regret,you can
feel it,down to the wood paneling...
Tommy... 你俩进来陪着Taylor吧
Tommy... Can you two
stay here with Taylor?
- 你要去哪
- 这老房子总跳闸
- Where are you going?
- It's an old house,fuses blow all the time,
应该没事 进来吧... 好的
it's probably nothing,just
please... Come on. Ok.
他在这
He's here.
那孩子在哪
Where's the child?
这房子太大了 我可不想挨个房间搜查
This house is quite large and I don't
particularly care to check every room.
很好
Very well.
敬酒不吃吃罚酒
Have it your way.
- Laurel... Laurel 别去...
- 不 Ollie还在外面
- Laurel... Laurel,don't...
- No,Ollie is still out there.
你在那岛上究竟经历了什么
What happened to you on that island?
你很快就会知道了
You're about to find out.
被拨火棍捅死
Death by poker.
这死法倒是很新奇
That's a new one.
他原本要开枪打我
He was going to shoot me.
然后... Robbins先生抓起拨火棍...
救了我一命
And then,uh,mister... Robbins,he
grabbed the poker and... saved my life.
Robbins先生才是真英雄
Mr. Robbins was a real hero.
要是没有他 我们早就都没命了
If it weren't for him,we'd all be dead.
好了 我知道该怎么写案件报告了
I've got enough details for my report.
我这就撤走我的人
I'll clear my boys out of here.
走吧
Let's go.
你还爱她 对吧
You still love her. Don't you?
我的感受并不重要
It doesn't matter how I feel.
因为我的所作所为...
我永远不可能和她在一起
Because of what I do...
I could never be with her.
你用不着害怕
You see,you don't have
anything to be afraid of.
她永远... 都绝不会知道我的秘密
She is never... ever
going to know my secret.
她知不知道并不重要
It doesn't matter if she knows.
我知道就行
I know.
我知道如果她发现你的身份
她会毫不犹豫地选择你
And I don't know how to be with
Laurel knowing the entire time...
我已不知该如何与Laurel相处了
that if she ever found out who you
really are... she would choose you.
感谢你为Eric和Nancy作出的努力
Thank you for everything you
tried to do for Eric and Nancy.
以及保护Taylor的安全
And for keeping Taylor safe.
过来
Come here.
你要乖哦 听到没
You keep being a good boy,ok?
Tommy 我十分需要和你谈谈...
Tommy,I really need to talk to you...
- 这是什么意思
- 拎包走人
- What's that for?
- It's my stuff.
怎么了
What's going on?
我不确定能否如你所期望一般付出
I'm not sure that I'm ready for the kind
of commitment that you're looking for.
长痛不如短痛 所以...
I don't want to hurt
you in the long run,so...
等等 我们差点死了
我现在情绪也很不稳定 你肯定不是认真的吧
Wait. We both almost lost our lives,and
I'm emotional,too,but you can't be serious.
我是认真的 Laurel
This is me serious,Laurel.
但是... 但这完全说不通啊
为什么... 为什么要现在说分手
But... But it doesn't make any
sense,I mean,why... Why now?
你为什么要跟我分手
Why even at all?
我曾以为这就是我想要的
I thought that I wanted this.
你
You.
但那晚我意识到事实并非如此
And the other night
made me realize I don't.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
我没有
I am not a liar.
如果你真的改变了
我也知道你确实变了 那你就不会...
If you've changed,and I know that
you've changed,then you wouldn't...
你不会这样对我
you would never do this.
大概我并未如想象中变化那么大吧
Then I guess I haven't changed
as much as we all thought,then.
我知道
I know.
你觉得我就是个白痴
You think I'm an idiot.
我一直觉得你是个白痴
I always thought you were an idiot.
我现在觉得你根本就是脑死亡
Now I think you're brain dead.
可能你还真说对了
Yeah,you're probably right.
我不明白 Roy
Look,I don't understand this,Roy.
为什么你非要找到帽衫男
Why is finding the Hood
so important to you?
那晚的场景不停在我脑海中回放
I can't stop replaying
that night in my head.
那晚我被那个变态抓住
The night I got
kidnapped by that psycho,
我以为我要死了
I just... I thought I was going to die.
- 但你活下来了
- 是啊 都是他的功劳
- But you didn't.
- Yeah,because of him.
你不欠他什么
You don't owe him anything.
你错了 我的一切都是他给的
You're wrong,I owe him everything.
我已无法回到过去的生活方式了 Thea
And I can't go back to
the way things were,Thea,
我不能继续平庸下去
I can't just go back to being nothing.
是你告诉我 我可以变得更好
You're the one that keeps telling me
that I can be better than who I am,
而这... 就是我改变的机会
and this... This is my chance to be.
我说不清 但是...
就好像我的生活与他息息相关
I can't explain it,but... It feels
like my life is connected to his.
那就去找他吧
So let's find him.
我知道这对你很重要
I can tell this means the world to you.
而你也对我很重要
And you mean the world to me.
所以去找他吧
So let's find him.
咱俩一起去
You and me.
义务警员 我们来啦
Vigilante,here we come.
一猜你就在这
Was hoping you'd be here.
我希望我们能统一思想
I want us to get back on the same page.
Oliver 我们根本就不是一个世界的人
至少以后不再是了
Oliver,we're not even in the
same book,you and me,not anymore.
我只是做了我觉得自己该做的事
I just did what I thought I had to.
我也一样
Just like I'm doing what I have to.
咱俩就此为止吧
We're done.
别这样
Don't do this.
你要么一箭射死我 要么就放我走
The only thing you have to stop me
from going out that door is an arrow.
他要去哪
Where's he going?
我们的罗宾汉表现如何啊
So how did our Robin Hood do?
意料之中的烂
As expected?
还是好好定个计划吧
So back to the drawing board we go.
姚飞
Yao Fei!
爸
Ba!
你怎么逃出来的
How did you escape?
我没逃出来
I didn't.
你这狗娘养的...
You son of a bitch...
你在岛上的日子到头了
Your time on this island is at an end.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 骗骗米 Ducky Rosemary 胖梨
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴:3P
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第二十集 完
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 20
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo